(Raj:)You will be faced with a total
often puzzles! (ECHOING)
Each-- (COUGHS)
(Raj:)Each... each puzzle will lead you
(Raj:)to the location of the next,
(Raj:)the last of which
will lead you to the coin. (ECHOING)
The first team that Ends it... wins!
(Sheldon:)He is a born showman.
Any questions? (ECHOING)
(Howard:)Yes, to be fair, do people who went
to Princeton get a head start?
That's not funny.
Oh, it actually ls,
if you get the joke.
(Sheldon:)It's based on the premise that
Princeton isn't a very good school.
(Leonard:)Ha-ha.
(Sheldon:)Oh, see? Now, he gets it.
(Raj:)Okay, guys, go ahead and divide
yourselves into teams of two.
(Bernadette:)-Should we just do couples?
-Couples sounds great.